FREEDOM OGUN

Graphic Design/Frontend Developer

+2347058341927,+2349045711488 | freedomogun192@gmail.com | Portfolio | LinkedIn | GitHub Portfolio website

ABOUT ME

I am a skilled graphic designer with three years of experience in the field, including one year specializing in product design. Continuously seeking growth, I am now focusing on web development, where I have successfully designed and developed two websites. Passionate about blending my creative expertise with technological advancements, I strive to deliver visually stunning and functional designs.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Technologies: Graphics Designs, Product Design, Packaging Design, Branding Design, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, NodeJS, Express, jQuery.

Tools: Photoshop, Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, GitHub, Netlify, Visual Studio, Postman.

Personal projects

Fresh green (skills: UI design, user experience)

Created a mobile app wireframe and converted it into a user-friendly mobile application
 Link: Fresh-green

<u>Jmega Electric</u> (skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, responsive design)

Built a fully responsive website for Jmega Electric. This project demonstrates my ability to create
and utilize my web development skills to enhance user experience and increase engagement.

Link: <u>Jmega</u>

EXPERIENCE

Company: Chrisat Enterprises

Location: BENIN CITY, EDO STATE, NIGERIA

2022-PRESENT

Project Description: Worked as a remote Graphics Designer and Frontend Developer by creating a company website.

- Revamp chrisat old logo and brand styles
- Create engaging social media flyers designs use for brand promotion
- Mockup presentation of chrisat branding and simple motion video
- Create an elegant website for chrisat Enterprises website Link

Company: Affinitx Cloud Storage Company

Location: LAGOS STATE, NIGERIA

Contract

Project Description: Logo branding and 3D Mockup presentation

- Modified brand style and guideline.
- 3D logo design and Mockup presentation.
- Interacted with client throughout the design phase.

Company: Hycab Taxi Service

Location: OWERRE, IMO STATE, NIGERIA

Jan 2022 - June 2022

Project Description: Designed flyers used for Facebook and Instagram Ads.

- Designed Flyers used for Facebook ads with positive feedback
- Create interactive social media designs for brand promotion
- Work alongside the CEO in making designs decision.

Company: Leadway Crypto Location: ABUJA, NIGERIA

Contract

Project Description: Designed flyers used for brand and sales promotion.

- Designs 7 brand flyers for brand promotion.
- Proper use of 3d assets and catchy element in each design.
- Work under a time limit for the total project.

Company: Pixels Bird
Location: REMOTE
2019— PRESENT

Project Description: Working remotely for different brands and clients.

- Create multiple designs for different brands
- Create unique and appealing logo and brand identity working freelancing
- Design several UI designs including mobile apps and website
- Work with client of different taste and style
- Strict adhere to client requirement and deadline
- build a website for a Jmega electric Website Link

OTHER SKILLS

Phone And Laptop Repair 2021-Present

Zoom Administrator 2021-Present

EDUCATION

Undergraduate

UNIVERSITY OF BENIN

Bachelor's Degree in Industrial Engineering (in view) 2019-2024

LEARNING AND CERTIFICATION

Product Design (UI/UX), Udemy
Full Stack development Bootcamp, Udemy (in view)

REFERENCE

Available on request